## Rahmat Fabhian Aminuddin

Tangerang, Banten | +62 878 8884 4782 | E-mail: abhifabhian@outlook.com | Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/rfabhian/ | Portofolio: www.abhifabhian.site

### **SUMMARY**

Fabhian is a focused and highly motivated person. He is really excited to learn new things and having new experiences in technology, product management, business and information system fields. Fabhian has proven success of several activities that required the capability of leadership, teamwork, focus group discussion (FGD), etc! He always tries to do his best in order to finish the responsibility he'd been given and is also passionate to participate in any competition, manage several projects, and working with many new people to exchange new ideas upon any things he does.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Information and System Technology, Institut Teknologi Bandung | 2019 - 2023 (expected)

• Relevant Coursework: Product Development, System Requirement Analysis, Enterprise Requirement Analysis, IT Resource Management, IST Services, Human Computer Interaction, Software Engineering, Object Oriented Programming.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Deal With Pengkom | Co-founder, Project Leader | May 2021 - Present

- Deal With Pengkom (DWP) is an online education learning platform with a goal to educate freshman students of any campus in Indonesia about the basic of Python Programming.
- Pioneered and currently leading this project, which taking several responsibilities such as business development, product management, user research, operational needs, marketing strategy, financial management and many more related to any need to improve this project, financially and progressively.
- DWP managed to get 1000+ accounts reached and 500+ profile activity on Instagram. Then, successfully gained 100+ product users in its first sale with a target market of only Institut Teknologi Bandung's freshman year students.

#### Bangkit Academy led by Google, Tokopedia, Gojek, & Traveloka| Android Development Trainee | Feb 2022 - Present

- Bangkit is a unique career readiness program led by Google and delivered with support from industry experts from our
  partners like Gojek, GoTo and Google. The program is designed to provide the participants with first-hand exposure
  to real-world practitioners and prepare them with relevant skills for a successful career in leading tech companies.
- Joined to learn about Android Development, with an ultimate goal to hone Fabhian's skills in many aspects.
- Selected in top **3,000 trainee out of 63,000+** applicants.

## ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Kabinet Keluarga Mahasiswa ITB (KM ITB) | Deputy Minister of Information System and Service Ministry | September 2021 - Present

- Kabinet KM ITB is the highest-level executive in student's activities for Institut Teknologi Bandung. Kabinet KM ITB coordinate the students' association and students' activities club in campus.
- Work closely with 9 Coordinating Ministries at Kabinet KM ITB while also supervising 2 General Directors and 7 staffs to provide a sustainable system services for Kabinet KM ITB.
- Coordinate the ministry with the Minister and has successfully launched 2 system services while also working on another 2 system services.
- Here are the **4 system services** that are being worked:
  - o KM ITB's Open Recruitment Website Page, can be accessed via km.itb.ac.id/oprec/
  - o Talent Management of KM ITB's Education Learning Website, can be accessed via akarasalearning.live/
  - General Secretary of KM ITB's One Stop Service Website, can be accessed via <u>bit.ly/KMS-KM2021</u>
  - o KM ITB's Knowledge Management System, ongoing project.

## **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

#### Performance Director | Creative Campaign Team of KM ITB's Presidential Candidate | March 2021 - April 2021

- Work closely in a **Core Campaign Team with 9 other Directors** to succeed the campaign of KM ITB's Presidential Candidate, Muhammad Hanif Syuhada.
- Responsible to ideate, evaluate and direct Hanif's public appearance on Instagram live campaign, Youtube live campaign, hearing campaign, and debate.
- Successfully finished the task with the win of Muhammad Hanif Syuhada as the President of KM ITB.

### **HONORS AND AWARDS**

• Awardee and Delegate of Ruang Kreasi IYLP to South Korea 2021

Awarded in the top 30 from 1000+ applicants to join the International Youth Leadership Program (IYLP) to South Korea.

Third Winner of BIST Business Case Buster 2021

Ranked 3<sup>rd</sup> by proposing an expansion for the case by quantifying the social impacts of the organization.

## SKILLS

- Languages: Indonesian (Native or bilingual proficiency), English (Professional working proficiency).
- Interpersonal Skills: Leadership, Time Management, Communication, Project Management, Product Management.
- Programming: Python, Java, Kotlin, C, HTML, CSS, MySQL.
- Design: Canva, Figma, Picsart.